(upbeat music)
Amazon Brand Registry can help you protect
and grow your brand in the Amazon store.
To participate, you'll need to have a registered
or pending trademark and your brand name or logo
permanently affixed to your products or packaging.
Once enrolled, you gain increased control
over your product detail pages.
Your registered trademark establishes legal rights
while Amazon's technology actively monitors
for counterfeits and IP violations.
Brand Registry offers multi-layered protection
with powerful tools and programs to safeguard your brand.
As a rights owner for your brand,
you can report infringement through report a violation,
prevent counterfeits with the transparency program,
remove unauthorized listings with Project Zero,
and partner with Amazon's counterfeit crimes unit
to take legal action against unauthorized sellers.
You'll also have opportunities to optimize your listings
and expand your brand's presence
with tools like A+ content,
as well as gain valuable insights
from customer reviews and programs like Amazon Vine.
Brand Registry can help you grow your customer base
through multiple channels,
create targeted advertising campaigns
with sponsored brands and sponsored display ads,
engage shoppers with dynamic content
through posts and Amazon live streams,
and build repeat business with subscribe
and save delivery discounts.
Track and optimize your performance
with powerful analytics tools like brand analytics
or test different versions of your content
with manage your experiments
to discover what resonates best with customers
and drives growth.
The more tools you use,
the stronger your brand presence on the Amazon store
can become.
Not sure you're ready for Brand Registry?
Review our Prepare to Enroll in Brand Registry checklist
to find out how you can work toward becoming eligible.
Visit the Brand Registry website
to explore all the benefits of the program
and begin enrollment.
(
upbeat music)